When we lose someone
from the neighborhood.
we all feel it.
[Jimmy] What I'd like to know
is who the fuck would
do Pat
in our own backyard?
[Sweeney]
Had a little talk with Danny.
Aw. I appreciate that.
It's a little more complicated.
-[grunts]
-He thinks I gave the order
and you killed Pat Murphy.
If you want to keep him alive.
keep him out
of Hell's Kitchen.
[Polk] You're asking me
to use federal pull
to ship your kid to a safe house
disguised as a clinic.
[Bridget] I talked to Cahill.
Well. it turns out
he doesn't need the weapon.
I'm sorry. Brendan.
It's gone.
But he does need me.
My target.
Colonel Gerald Markham.
The man who killed
your parents.
This is fucking dangerous.
[Bridget]
And what you do isn't?
I took six kilos from that disco
before we burned it down.
But if we don't deal it.
someone else will.
and they'll just become stronger
and more of a threat to us.
I think it's worth the risk.
We don't deal drugs.
[Mickey] I can't believe
we're back to this
nickel and dime shit.
Your Mr. Sweeney
just donated $100.000!
You think
Sweeney sold our coke?
Fuck yeah. I do.
Eamon Sweeney
with six fucking keys.
-[Sweeney] How much?
-Give you 40 apiece
for the first five.
35 for everything after that.
[Gotti] Eamon Sweeney himself
sold it to Leon?
-That's right.
-So. what's our next move?
[Gotti] Kill that motherfucker
Eamon Sweeney.
I just can't believe
he lied to my fucking face.
Problem is.
you put Sweeney on a pedestal.
We all did.
To Eamon Sweeney.
for always looking out
for the less fortunate.
But now we know
he don't fucking belong there.
He has your loyalty. right?
You would die for that
motherfucker. I know you.
[gunshots]
You think
he'd say the same for you?
Looks like the Italians
weren't too happy with you
selling that coke.
You wanna get a beer?
[sinister music]
[Sweeney]
You know me. Paul.
I wouldn't have asked
for this sit down
if I didn't think
it was in your best interests.
[Gotti]
This guy's threatening war?
I'll send his Irish Mick crew
back to potato land
in a fuckin' box.
[Sweeney] Yeah. those
two hitmen you sent after me
are in fuckin' boxes
right now. John.
Happy to make
the same arrangement for you.
Settle down. both of you.
We're here to talk.
You make a move against Eamon?
Of course not. I don't know
anything about this shit.
He used hitmen
from Scarfa's crew.
Angelo Bruno knows
all about it. Ask him.
Who gives a shit what that mopey
motherfucker Angelo Bruno says?
That guy's a fuckin' liar.
Angelo's a boss.
I trust bosses.
How about you. Paul?
[chuckles]
This is why I hate drugs. hmm?
Shit like this happens.
You think
Angelo Bruno's a liar?
I'll call him
and tell him you said that.
And if Eamon's story
checks out...
...you and I will have
a problem.
Understand?
Or...
we can agree
to resolve this issue
right here. right now.
Because there's a federal
fucking task force out there
tryin' to put me
in fuckin' jail!
And they're not
interested in you or you.
So I don't want
dead fuckin' bodies piling up
that lead back to me!
Which is why
I don't want neither of you
dealing narcotics!
Can you get that
through your fuckin' heads?
Yeah. you think you're talking
to John right now. right?
Because I don't
fuckin' deal drugs.
Fuck yourself. Sweeney.
Neither do I.
I want you two
to make peace.
Whatever your gripes are.
put it behind you.
Eamon Sweeney is
not to be touched.
Or anyone in my crew.
[Paul]
You got that. John?
Not Eamon
nor any of his crew.
I can't hear you. John.
Not to be touched.
Good.
Now shake.
[tense music]
[punk rock theme music]
-♪ It didn't take long ♪
-♪ I didn't get far ♪
♪ Before the cops were told ♪
-♪ That I'd stolen the car ♪
-♪ Stolen the car ♪
-♪ There was an APB ♪
-♪ APB ♪
-♪ Sent out for me ♪
-♪ Out for me ♪
♪ Ratted out by my own ♪
♪ Now I'm a public enemy ♪
♪ I'm a Catholic school kid ♪
-♪ I'm an altar boy ♪
-♪ Altar boy ♪
♪ I was dropped on my head ♪
-♪ Now I'm here to destroy ♪
-♪ Here to destroy ♪
-♪ I'm a stone-cold killer ♪
-♪ Stone-cold killer ♪
-♪ In the CYO ♪
-♪ CYO ♪
♪ I'm lining them up ♪
♪ And I'm laying them low ♪
♪ But honest as the day
is long that's a fact ♪
♪ I'm not nearly half
as bad as I act ♪
♪ See. I'm always wrong
in the eyes of the law ♪
♪ Parents and priests say
it's the final straw ♪
♪ But sure as the sun.
it rises and sets ♪
This whiskey was casked in '22.
That's before the Depression.
It's almost as old as I am.
[chuckles]
Only 40 cases ever sold.
[coughs]
Oh. Jesus.
That's got quite a kick.
This is liquid bliss.
If you don't mind me saying.
I've had similar reactions
to cough syrup.
[chuckles]
I guess
it's an acquired taste.
So. I take it
the meeting went well.
Gotti got spanked.
No more narcotics.
but...
Big Paul wants me
to basically ignore the fact
that cocksucker sent
two fuckin' hitmen after me.
Do we go after Gotti?
No. I got a better way
to get that motherfucker back.
He's not allowed
to sell drugs. right?
So... we will.
[chuckles]
Okay. Uh. Castellano's
all right with that?
He doesn't have to know.
Look. Jimmy. you were right.
Okay. it makes sense for us
to get into narcotics.
We don't.
somebody else will.
they're gonna get richer
and stronger while we stand pat.
Well. you know I agree.
But I stole that coke
from the Colombians
'cause I happened
to be there.
I mean. we sure as hell
can't go back to them.
I'm gonna
introduce you to Leon.
dude that shylocks for us
up in Harlem.
He can get you supply.
-What about money?
-I'll cover that.
But you gotta do this
on your own. Okay?
I gotta stay on good terms
with Castellano.
Of course.
[Sweeney] And ya gotta
be careful. Jimmy.
This cocaine.
it's a nasty
fuckin' business.
You can't trust anybody.
Slàinte.
[Polk]
It's hot as a bitch outside.
and the A/C
in this place is for shit.
[Glenn]
Tax dollars at work.
Any word on Danny?
Oh. I hear he's doing fine.
He's only been
disciplined twice.
He hit one of the counselors
and threatened the other one
with cutting her throat.
-I see.
-But let's talk about you!
What about me?
You know. when I invited you
to join this task force.
my superior officers
thought I was crazy.
"He's corrupt." they said.
I said. "So's everybody
at Midtown North."
I said. "You've got to use
a criminal to catch a criminal."
But you. as far as
useful criminals go.
you've been
pretty fuckin' useless!
Does this mean
I'm gettin' fired?
No. it means
you're gonna wear a wire.
What? What.
are you fucking serious?
You tryin' to get me killed?
Get Sweeney on tape
talkin' about something
-we can arrest him for.
-Fuck that. I won't do it.
Then Danny won't get
the help he needs.
I'll have him released.
and he'll be right back
where he started.
You would do that?
Which is it?
-[microphone feedback]
-You got it?
Yeah. Fine.
[Polk]
You got a lotta tattoos there.
Yeah.
Swift. silent. deadly.
Force Recon motto. right?
Yeah.
Legendary.
I'm betting you were
deep in the shit.
You know.
our enemy over there
were a bunch of gooks
I didn't know.
Betraying my friends
is different.
You're working for your country.
same as you were doing then.
Yeah. semantics.
Sweeney's a smart guy.
He won't talk.
It's your job
to make him talk.
This guy is
a serious street guy.
not some dipshit novice.
He can spot the fuckin' heat
in a 40-acre field.
Who's his most trusted man?
It's a toss-up
between Eddie Breen
and Dukey Sullivan.
probably Breen.
Tell him Eddie Breen is one
of our confidential informants
and he's been talkin' to me.
No way he'd buy
Breen would talk.
Maybe yes. maybe no...
so plant that seed with care.
I'm gonna hide the recorder
down your pants.
Be careful
when you're sitting down.
[clicking]
[Brendan]
This is Colonel Markham.
He arrived in Northern Ireland
not long after Bloody Sunday.
They found
this wee sadistic prick
to try and stop our movement.
He implemented
aggressive house searches.
internment without trial.
and shootin'
before asking questions.
Now. as you know...
he was also responsible
for the murder
of Bridget's family...
Tadhg and Maureen McKenna
and those two wee boys...
...all heroes
to the cause in my eyes.
He arrives next month
on the 14th.
and he's being given an award
at the British Consulate.
It's like they're
throwing it in our faces.
The more Irish Catholics
they kill. the bigger the prize.
Aye. They want the world
to think that black is white.
up is down.
Want to rewrite the narrative.
bury British crimes.
And it's up to us.
mo chairde.
to give the world
a wee dose of reality.
Now. the Consulate is
on 48th and Second.
We're gonna put the car
right at the entrance.
and we're gonna blow this
motherfucker to smithereens.
This is why you wanted
the rocket launcher.
And now that's gone...
there's another way.
Semtex.
A car bomb?
No. no. I don't know
about that. Brendan.
I'm the leader of this cell.
it's my decision.
Now. if we're lucky.
only Markham
and his security detail
will be killed.
Yeah. but you know
the chances of that are slim.
So. there's gonna be
civilian casualties and...
This is a war. Bridget.
Or have you forgotten that?
[Seamus]
Lock up when you're done.
[Mickey]
All right. thank you.
[Jimmy]
Yeah. thanks. Seamus.
Hey. Seamus.
it's as hot as balls.
You got any cold beers?
In the ice chest.
-You're a fuckin' hero.
-Yeah. yeah.
This Leon guy. he all right?
I've never met him.
I know. but is he
a straight shooter?
Well. Sweeney seems
to think so.
and he's fuckin'
paying for it so...
I need a fuckin' beer.
Hey. hold on. He's here.
[funk music playing
from car stereo]
You Roarke?
Hello. Leon.
This is my associate. Mickey.
This my guy. Charlie.
[Jimmy]
Thanks for coming.
Didn't expect Sweeney's name
and blow to come back so fast.
Must've got a taste
of that cash.
He's not involved.
This is private.
-Just the two of you?
-Uh-huh.
-Boss. this is fucked up.
-No. Hold up. Hold up.
How much you two lookin' for?
-Three keys.
-[scoffs]
You got that kind of bread?
That's 150 large. son.
Mm. from what I understand.
the wholesale price is
35 a key. so...
So. you think I'm gonna risk
my Black ass for free?
Nah. white boy.
I got to get my cut.
It's 50 per key.
take it or leave it.
You'll still come out on top.
All right.
Let's start with two keys.
If this goes well. maybe we can
talk about that price. huh?
Let me ask you somethin'.
Do you two even know
what the fuck you are doing?
You know
how to cut this shit up?
That's a no.
Okay. 'cause of Sweeney.
I'm gonna explain this
to you real simple.
You cut the shit one to one
with baby laxative
or inositol.
You chop it fine.
You press it with heat
to maintain weight.
You keep your press.
you keep your cutter.
and you keep your stash
in separate places.
If you get raided and all
that shit's in the same place.
intent to distribute.
that's five years.
-Automatic.
-You should teach
a fuckin' seminar.
-Control your fuckin' dog.
-Hey.
Apologies. Thanks. Leon.
So. back to business.
When and where?
Forty-seventh and Tenth.
Tonight.
Around 11.
Bring the cash.
we bring the bricks.
One more thing.
You white niggers get caught
and dime me out.
I will kill you both
and your whole fuckin' families.
[car starting]
[funk music playing
on car stereo]
What would we do
if that Javits Center
wasn't being built
in our neck of the woods. huh?
-Stand in line for soup?
-Fuck that.
Bored out of our fuckin' tits
is what we'd be doing.
Probably both.
Hi. Glenn. What's up?
I want to talk to you.
Privately.
No secrets between me
and Eamon. Glenn.
you know that. right?
It's personal.
Who gives a fuck?
We own you.
Don't get fresh. Dukey.
or I'll slap
that fuckin' taste
right out of your mouth.
[Sweeney] All right.
all right. cut it out.
Let's. uh. get that cut
to our Italian friends.
and. uh.
let's go have a chat.
Half-ass-copper
piece of shit.
Leave it out. will ya?
Dukey's not a big fan
of the boys in blue.
Yeah. no shit.
All right.
What can I do ya for?
I wanted to talk to you
about Eddie.
What about Eddie?
He's been talking
to the feds.
Fuck you! No way.
I saw his name on a list
of confidential informants.
I'm sorry. I'm just
tellin' you what I saw.
There's no fuckin' way
Eddie Breen
is talkin'
to the fuckin' feds.
Eamon. You fuckin' pay me
to tell you things
you might not
wanna hear. okay?
Up to you
what you do with it.
Wait. wait. wait.
Where did you see this list?
On Agent Polk's desk
when she was in the john.
Ask him.
I'm sure he'll deny it.
Fuck. I would. too.
But let me do
a little more diggin' around.
see what I can find.
Yeah. you do that.
I gotta ask ya.
What's Eddie have on ya?
What do you mean.
have on me?
No. I'm sayin' what if.
God forbid.
he had to testify.
how could he hurt you?
I mean.
has he witnessed murders?
Fuck you.
I don't fuckin'
believe this.
Fine.
No. No fuckin' way.
Eddie Breen is solid
as a fuckin' rock.
I'm just saying what I saw.
That's all.
Let me look into it more
on my end. all right?
-I'll see you later.
-Yeah.
[scoffs]
[door shutting]
[Bridget]
Jesus fucking Christ.
Hey. calm the fuck down.
all right? I didn't steal it.
That looks like a small bank.
-It's business.
-Whose business?
Sweeney's backin' a move.
What's the move?
Don't say selling T-shirts.
-What do you think it is?
-Hm.
Oh. so we're not buying
the house in the Catskills.
No. we're buying time
in federal prison.
Look. this is
strategic. Bridget.
-Big money. low exposure.
-Every drug dealer
says that
at the beginning.
-Oh. yeah?
-Yeah. yeah. yeah.
We have drug dealers
in Ireland too. you know.
Look. I'm just-- I'm tryin'
to plan ahead. all right?
-Yeah.
-The future. our future.
-Okay.
-I mean. come on.
you don't want our kids
running around in this
fuckin' building. do you?
How do we have kids. Jimmy?
Every other day.
you and I are one step away
from blowing ourselves up
or throwing ourselves in jail.
It won't be forever.
When my ma died
in her own bed...
'cause we couldn't
afford a real doctor...
I swore to myself I-I would
never let that happen again.
And if coke's the way
to avoid that...
...then coke it is.
[sighs]
I love you. Jimmy.
I just want you
to stay out of prison.
And I wish the same for you.
[soft music]
[Glenn on mic] No. I'm sayin'.
what if. God forbid.
he had to testify.
how could he hurt you?
I mean.
has he witnessed murders?
[Sweeney] Fuck you.
I'd call that a fail.
He was never gonna believe
Eddie Breen was talkin' to you.
I told you this before.
We have to make him believe!
I want you to arrest Breen.
Ugh. You know.
it never ends with you.
Why me? You do it.
So Sweeney thinks
you're involved.
Then he'll be sure to talk
to you about a lot of things.
Who you trying to entrap here.
me or Sweeney?
We already know
you're on Sweeney's pad.
we're clear on that.
You're not guilty
of any other crimes. right?
Is that a serious question?
Then you have nothing
to worry about.
And I'm supposed to trust you?
Why should I?
I could ask the same question.
Okay. he talks.
I want immunity
on everything.
You know
that's not gonna happen.
So. what? You're just gonna
throw me to the fuckin' wolves
and hope for the best.
that's bullshit.
You used to be a marine
and a very good cop!
Do something right for once.
I'll give you immunity
on everything.
Except murder. Deal?
Yeah.
[rock music playing]
[Connor] Hold on.
Let me get this straight.
Mr. Sweeney says
we can't sell the coke.
then he says
we can sell the coke.
just as long as he don't know
that we're sellin' the coke.
That's right. And then
when we do sell the coke.
we gotta pay him
for sellin' the coke
but act like
we're not sellin' the coke.
Is that right?
Yeah. Something like that.
This fucking guy is
unbelievable.
Nah. that actually
makes sense to me.
-That makes sense.
-Of course it does.
'Cause you're
a fuckin' cokehead.
It's the breakfast
of champions!
I'm just actually looking
forward to having my own stash.
-Free samples.
-Hey.
We're not consumers.
we're sellers.
Goes out the door. not up
your fuckin' noses. alright?
If you put it like that.
Jimmy. I'm fuckin' out.
Oh. and did I forget
to mention
it's gonna make you
filthy fucking rich?
-Oh. yeah. I'm back in then.
-Yeah. I bet you are.
-I'm fuckin' in.
-Okay. so.
we get this blow.
And then what's the plan?
We start selling.
Now. there's 20. 30 joints
between Ninth and Eleventh.
Irish bars. sailor bars.
strip clubs.
all filled to the brim
with fuckin' cokeheads.
-No offense.
-None taken.
Then we got the unions.
Longshoremen.
dock-rats. you know.
guys who'd rather
move powder than crates.
Yeah. and don't forget those
little snot-nosed yuppies
with polo shirts
and trust funds.
makin' Wall Street
all that money.
All those guys think about
is getting fucked up.
For them.
it's a hundred bucks a gram.
It's pocket change
for those soft fucks.
-Fuck. yeah.
-And...
Sweeney's frontin' us
the cash for the first load.
How much. Jimmy?
Hundred grand.
You got that on you?
I'm meeting Leon tonight.
Fuck. We're all going
with you. right?
Yeah. with our fuckin'
guns loaded. we are.
No. no. no. All right.
he's Sweeney's guy.
I don't need to bring
the whole lot of youse.
Besides. I don't want him
to think we're a bunch
-of fuckin' amateurs.
-But Jimmy.
we are a bunch
of fuckin' amateurs.
[laughter]
[Bridget] Well. my father was
a history teacher
in a Catholic school
just outside of Newry.
They pegged him
as a revolutionary.
And they were not wrong.
Her father not only brought
more volunteers to the cause
than any other man.
he organized weapon routes.
covert communications.
He inspired us greatly.
I came face to face
with Colonel Markham
when I was
in the Maze prison.
Like most
of these fuckers...
first he tried
to befriend me.
When I wouldn't talk.
the torture began.
Started with
psychological games...
saying that my family
had turned me in.
And then sleep deprivation.
And beatings.
Then he broke my bones.
Fingers and toes first.
The worst...
was solitary confinement
for months at a time.
I thought I'd go mad.
I did. for a while.
I've gathered photos
and details of Markham
that we all need to study.
Together...
we can pay back
this fucking bastard.
We will. Brendan.
You can count on us.
You can count on me. too.
[somber music]
[♪ The Message ♪ by Grandmaster
Flash and the Furious Five]
[knocking on window]
Hey.
Sweeney's guy.
How's it goin'?
Good.
-You met Charlie.
-Hey. Charlie.
What's up?
Got the bread?
Got it right here.
-Hundred K?
-Mm-hm.
Well. it came from Sweeney.
so I ain't gotta
count it. right?
It's all there.
Charlie?
Careful when
you open that up. kid.
Just take a quick look.
It's good.
Two keys.
Yeah. looks good.
Hopefully. this is
just the beginning.
Well. right on.
[Charlie]
Just one second. Leon.
Yeah. what?
[Jimmy]
What the fuck?
[Charlie]
Shut the fuck up.
Gimme the money.
Gimme the coke.
Toss it into the front seat.
Do it fast or I'll blow
your motherfuckin' head off.
You know you're gonna die
for this. right?
[chuckles]
Nah.
Gotti says you are.
[gunshot]
[gasping]
♪ But now I sing
the sad. sad song ♪
♪ Of how you live so fast
and die so young ♪
♪ So don't push me
'cause I'm close to the edge ♪
♪ I'm trying
not to lose my head ♪
♪ Ha-ha. ha ha ♪
♪ It's like a jungle sometimes.
it makes me wonder ♪
[Mickey]
Hey. let's go!
♪ It's like a jungle sometimes.
it makes me wonder ♪
♪ How I keep
from going under ♪♪
Fuck.
[panting]
[both laughing]
Wait. why the fuck
are we laughing?
I don't fuckin' know.
[laughing]
You know what?
Maybe I'm just laughing
about the fact we got this
and we got this.
-Fuck John Gotti!
-Shh! Bridget.
Hey. we're keeping this.
right. brother?
Jimmy?
We're keeping this. right?
I've gotta...
uh. go and...
clean this fucking shit off.
Come on.
Hey. Jimmy!
Shut the fuck up!
[breathing heavily]
[somber music]
Big money. low exposure.
Isn't that what you said?
[somber music]
[sizzling]
Charlie Bricks is dead.
-Where?
-Hell's Kitchen. Forty-Seventh.
Cops found him
with half a fuckin' head.
Fuckin' idiot.
Never should've trusted him.
Leon?
Him too.
looks like that Mick punk
he was supposed to meet
got the jump on him.
-What about the coke?
-Product's gone.
So's the 100K.
[clears throat]
So. who is this kid?
[Apreda] I've been
checking around. some kid
named Jimmy Roarke.
Sweeney's crew.
along with
that stronz Mickey Flanagan.
Maybe those two assholes are
smarter than I thought.
Sweeney wouldn't have
the balls to touch cocaine
after our meeting with Paul.
but that's not gonna stop
-this Roarke kid. right?
-What. you think
this kid would go
against his boss?
Everybody fucking does that.
I do it all the time.
You want
this Roarke guy clipped?
Let me talk to Paul.
Don't tell me
you sold that shit already.
No. not yet. It's being cut up
by the boys as we speak.
Your pal Leon's dead.
Yeah. turns out Charlie Bricks
was in Gotti's pocket
the whole fuckin' time.
He musta told him about the coke
I snatched from the nightclub.
which explains
why he sent hitmen against you.
So you got the money
and the coke.
-What about Charlie Bricks?
-Dead too.
Nasty fuckin' business.
Didn't I tell ya?
Anyway. I just thought
you should know.
Yeah.
Hey. Jimmy.
You coulda kept
this fuckin' money.
You know that. right?
I never woulda known.
It's not how I do business.
Appreciate it.
Fuck.
Poor Leon.
[sighs]
You're gonna have
to find a new connection.
And Gotti knows
you're dealing now. so...
...watch your back.
We're under Castellano's
protection. right?
So. Gotti can't touch us?
Only as long as Big Paul
thinks we're not dealing drugs.
[Gotti] They're gettin' ready
to move weight. Paul.
The Irish.
Which Irish?
Which Irish? Come on.
I'm askin'.
Sweeney's crew.
It's in motion.
So. you're saying Sweeney
disobeyed my orders
to sell narcotics?
No. no. no.
The younger ones.
Guys named Roarke
and Mickey Flanagan.
Ya remember Flanagan?
Vaguely. You got proof?
What? I need proof?
I know. I hear things.
There was this drug deal
on the West Side gone south.
and I think this Irish kid.
he whacked these two mulignans.
stole their coke.
This is exactly the type of shit
that you wanted to avoid. right?
Dead bodies all over the city.
So what do you want me to do?
Well. I want your permission
to whack these Irish bastards.
Sweeney's men?
Yes. Sweeney's men.
My answer's no.
I don't give a flying fuck
about the Irish.
Sweeney's problem.
But you...
you keep your nose out of it.
Ah. Paul this is just
the type of shit that you--
I don't want to hear you
selling coke behind my back.
Understood?
So why the fuck you got
a different standard for them?
Because they're animals. John.
Let them poison themselves.
We're men.
And we follow orders. right?
Of course. Yeah.
-Mm.
-You're the boss.
You got my loyalty. 100%.
Here you go. darling.
You're too kind.
To the Irish.
the only people who can start
a bar fight over poetry.
Some fights are worth having.
don't you think. Sergeant Kent?
Ex-sergeant.
Call me Randall.
And don't get me wrong.
I like poetry
as much as the next guy.
Do you have any favorites?
Sure. Dr. Seuss.
[cackles]
Mm. Partial
to Yeats myself.
Ah. you got one in ya?
Yeah.
Yeah. one my father taught me.
But where can we draw water.
said Pearse to Connolly.
When all the wells are
parched away?
O plain as plain can be.
There's nothing
but our own red blood
to make a right rose tree.
Well. I don't understand
what the fuck that means.
[laughing]
But it sure sounds good
coming outta your mouth.
Randall. let's get
down to business.
We wanna buy some Semtex.
Oh.
Oh. that's not
gonna be easy.
Grenades. M16s. no problem.
I'm not saying
it's impossible.
but it's gonna cost ya.
How much?
One million dollars.
[laughs]
Just takin' the piss.
I'll need 50.000.
That's fuckin' outrageous.
This is for a good cause.
Randall. are you Irish?
My father was Irish.
but my mother was
kind of a mutt.
I'm not sure.
Maybe German or French.
To be honest.
I never bothered to ask.
She's a bit of a cunt.
I prefer my father.
if that makes any difference.
Well. this is
for Irish independence.
[Randall]
A good cause.
But I've done my time
serving good causes.
Germany. Turkey. Vietnam.
I'm interested
in getting paid.
Fine.
We'll get you
the 50.000.
[laughs]
You toss in a bottle
of Irish whiskey.
and you have yourself a deal.
Here.
Take this as a down payment.
Where the fuck
did you find him?
Look at you.
-Where are we going?
-We're gonna go to my place.
I thought
we were gonna go see a show.
Some place
with air-conditioning?
Are you kidding me. honey?
You are the fucking show.
You and me and this chinky food.
a bit of fuckin' music.
We'll have a fuckin' great time.
[police siren]
-Eddie!
-Are you fucking for real?
-Let's go!
-Fuck sakes!
Put the fuckin' bag down.
-Fuck off!
-Come on.
[woman] Eddie!
Put your hands
on the fuckin' trunk.
Jesus fucking Christ!
Feds wanna chat you up.
You better not be packing.
[officer]
Keep moving. please.
Eamon's gonna hear about this.
you know that. yeah?
-I'm sure he will.
-You fucking cunt.
You keep a fuckin' civil tongue
in your head. Let's go.
How are ya. Mary?
Ya all right?
Yeah. Yeah.
Get in the fuckin' car.
[Breen] Deb. honey! Pick up
the fuckin' Chinese food!
Yeah. Ah!
Oh. here we go.
You got 15 ghost names
on Local 780 payrolls.
Not one of them ever
lifted a beam at Javits.
That's theft
of federal funds.
That looks great.
-What's it gotta do with me?
-Then there's
the no-show contracts
at Pier 76.
Same contractors.
We're connecting
the dots. Eddie.
Ah. you're connecting the dots.
are you? Well done. you!
Where the fuck's my lawyer?
I should tell you what.
lady. don't bother.
because you can't prove
any of this.
You want to know why?
'Cause none of it's true.
Ask Officer Keenan right there.
[Polk] Officer Keenan?
Why would I ask him?
'Cause he knows me.
Go on. Glenn.
Tell her she's talkin' shit.
Well. thing is Eddie.
she's got evidence.
Now. I'm lookin'
to help you out...
cut a deal with them.
It'll go easier for you.
Are you fuckin' for real?
You double-crossing prick.
[Polk] I got you on
conspiracy to commit fraud.
Maybe throw in a racketeering
predicate or two.
But I don't want you. Eddie.
Oh. no?
Why the fuck am I here then?
Because...
I want your boss.
Eamon Sweeney.
My boss Eamon Sweeney
is an upstanding
Irish-American citizen
who pays his taxes.
gives to the poor.
and creates jobs.
What the fuck do you do?
Eamon Sweeney's a thief...
...who milks
his own community dry
under the guise
of the working man.
You wanna go down with him?
Be my guest.
♪ Do you want your old lobby
washed down Con Shine ♪
♪ Do you want
your old lobby washed down ♪
♪ Says I. I'll take half
and says she. with a laugh ♪
♪ Do you want your old lobby
washed down. Con Shine ♪
So now what?
Wait till Eamon Sweeney
reaches out to you.
which I have
no doubt he will.
See what he has to say.
[Breen]
Yeah. have your little
fuckin' chats there. are ya?
You fuckin' prick. you.
-Holy shit.
-Hey. Declan.
Connor's waitin'
on that fuckin' laxative!
Holy fuckin' Christ.
I'm sweating
like a fuckin' dago.
Bag it up.
Yeah. take a look at that.
It's good. it's good.
But it's about consistency.
Keep them all
the same fuckin' size.
Let's go. Give me
that fuckin' laxative.
All right.
That enough?
Jeez. it's too much. I told ya.
I don't need that much.
And you're mixing that
one to one. right?
Of course.
I'm mixing it one to one.
-I need clean fucking product.
-Yeah. I'm very
fucking passionate
about my work.
so I do it right. okay?
It's good fuckin' work. boys.
We're about to make
some serious fuckin' money.
As long as that powder
goes in the bags
-and not up your fuckin' nose.
-I'm fine. Mick. I'm fine.
Holy. Mick. Mick.
Lighten up. okay?
Have a fuckin' bump.
Do a line.
No! You all heard
what Jimmy said. alright?
The product is for
the customers. it's not for us.
-Hey.
-Hey. Jimmy.
-How's it going?
-Jimmy.
-Hey. Jim.
-It's going good. Jimmy.
It's all moving
like clockwork.
We had some fuckin'
discipline problems with Sean.
-But we straightened that out.
-Hey. Sean.
maybe take it easy on that.
-you know?
-Yeah. I'm fine.
-What did I fuckin' tell you?
-And. uh...
and do me a favor
when you're done?
Can you just.
you know. make sure
you put everything
back to the way it was.
-you know. spick and span.
-Jimmy. you want a beer?
No. no.
I just came to get you.
I got a lead
on a potential buyer.
-so let's go.
-All right.
Oh. and bring
a couple of samples.
-Sure.
-Keep up the good work. boys.
Yes. Jimmy.
Sean. it's gotta
be consistent.
-I'm tryin'.
-Connor. watch him!
Yeah. I'm watchin' him.
Fuck.
Hey. you see Sean trying
to cut that shit?
Looked like he was bagging flour
at a fuckin' bakery.
Yeah. hopefully he learns
before he snorts himself stupid.
Don't move.
Don't fuckin' move.
The fuck are you doing?
Get in the fuckin' car.
Get the fuck off me!
You fuckin' dago cocksucker.
Fuck you.
[typewriter clacking]
[footsteps approaching]
Where is everyone?
Sent them home.
You know. the less people
who meet Randall. the better.
Mm-hmm.
For security?
Yeah.
I don't trust him. I do not
like the way he drinks.
Well. the weapon you lost
came off a freighter
from Liberia.
and that contact's well gone.
Randall's our best bet.
I am sorry to have put you
in that position.
[knocking on door]
Do you have the money?
Yes.
You have 50.000? Yeah?
-Yes.
-Where'd you get it?
Let's just say
I have very rich sponsors.
Oh. full of surprises.
aren't you?
Listen.
I only keep information
from you for your sake.
-Strictly professional.
-[knocking on door]
Get the door.
[Randall] You are gonna want
to be very careful with this.
I carried it here
myself by foot.
Couldn't trust
a car or subway.
Even without a blasting cap.
this stuff can be volatile.
-Where'd you get it?
-From the armory on Lexington.
I have a friend there.
He know about us?
Of course not.
He lets me in.
he turns the other way.
Of course. I did promise him
a nice payday
from all the money
you're gonna give me.
Speaking of which.
Oh. yeah. of course.
There you go.
Ah. you don't mind
if I take a peek. do ya?
Not that I don't trust
you fine Irish soldiers
fighting for a good cause.
Sure. count it all.
What's this?
[Brendan] Poetry.
Jesus Christ!
Why'd the fuck
did you just do that?
[Brendan]
Like you said. Bridget.
Can't have
a drunkard like him...
blabbering about us
to the highest bidder.
Hey. hey.
I did this
to protect the mission.
And you. Okay?
Come on.
So you got wind Eddie was
gonna get grabbed up.
you didn't think
I might wanna know?
Took me by surprise.
But I insisted on being in there
while they interrogated him.
-Oh. good. What'd he say?
-Yeah. well.
Fuckin' turns out the only
reason they brought him in
was to try to get him
to flip on you.
Hmm. Did he?
I gotta ask.
What have you done
that Breen knows about?
Eddie knows all about me.
Yeah. I know.
but I mean. specifically?
But. what do you mean.
like with the Javits Center?
[Glenn] Yeah.
Ah. he knows
about the skimming.
you know.
the no-show jobs. all of it.
And your deal with Castellano?
How many times
I gotta tell you. Glenn?
Eddie knows everything
there is to know about me.
But you can ask him yourself.
How are ya. Glenn?
Eddie. you're out.
[Breen] Yeah.
Eamon got me the best lawyer
money can buy. didn't he?
They wanted to keep me
in overnight. but fuck it.
-I'm here now.
-Nice.
Yeah.
Good. huh?
You stood up.
Good fuckin' job.
I'm relieved.
What? Come on. look.
I had no choice.
I had to bring you in
for those fucks. right?
I cannot tip my hand to them.
[Breen]
See. the problem is now. Glenn.
is I can't trust you.
-Don't say that.
-Neither do I.
[chuckles]
Get the fuck outta here!
Fucking cocksucker!
[grunting]
Motherfucker!
[shouting]
Grab. grab. grab him!
You fucking cunt.
Fuck you. motherfucker!
[grunts]
All right. all right. all right!
Can we take him outside now?
Jesus.
[grunts]
[grunting]
[grunting continues]
[Sweeney] Alright.
alright. enough. stop!
[grunting]
We can't kill him.
They know where he is.
Looks like maybe he fell down
a flight of stairs. right?
Probably drunk.
[Dukey]
That's right.
He fell down dead drunk
and wet himself. right. boys?
Okay.
-Oh-oh!
-You fucking piece of shit.
Wake up. asshole.
[gasps]
[groans]
[Sweeney] Hey. Glenn.
In case you're wondering. yeah.
You're off the pad.
[heavy breathing]
[Gotti] You boys know
what Manhattan's gonna be
in five years?
It's gonna be condos.
shiny towers.
cocaine in every club.
every party.
every fuckin' bathroom stall.
Whole island's
gonna run on powder.
That sounds like paradise.
Someone's gonna
own the pipeline.
I want it to be you.
My supply.
Your streets.
Fifty-fifty.
What the fuck did you just say?
It's pretty nice. right?
And what would
your boss think?
Castellano's a dinosaur.
He's still acting
like it's 1952.
and he's peddling olive oil
out of a fuckin' Buick.
At least your guy Sweeney was
willing to experiment.
Sweeney's concentrating
on the Javits Center.
The coke thing was
a one-off.
-He's not interested.
-Right.
But you're sittin' on two keys
and a hundred grand.
Which is gonna be gone
as soon as you peddle it.
So. how the fuck
are you gonna re-up?
You lost your guy Leon. Right?
You burned the Colombians.
who were my guys.
What. you think
I didn't know about all that?
Don't worry about it.
willing to forgive.
[chuckles]
So what the fuck
do you want from us?
Well. listen.
I've been moving weight since
before you two were pulling
on each other's peckers.
So I got connections
with other Latin crews.
You wanna play.
you're gonna need me.
Oh. I know you're loyal
to Sweeney. but come on.
let's be honest. where the fuck
is that heading. huh?
Javits gets built. Castellano
tosses him out like garbage.
And you? You're standing
on a job site in Queens.
with a wrench in one hand
and your dick in the other.
You wanna win. Jimmy.
you gotta come with me.
Let me just get this right.
Your fuckin' dogs here
pinch us off our streets.
put their fuckin' hands
on us. and now what?
You're offering us a job?
Well. I'm offering
you boys a future.
You don't want a future.
then an early grave.
[chuckling]
That's quite an offer.
But you know what?
And with
all due respect. John...
...you can go fuck yourself.
Your little lovers' tiff
with Big Paul.
that's your fuckin' business.
Not mine.
I'm not your salesman.
And I don't snake
the man who brought me up.
Jimmy.
You think that old
cocksucker's got your back?
[chuckling]
All bosses are snakes.
You don't know that?
We done here?
Yeah. I got a roast
in the oven.
I don't want it
getting burned.
Yeah. yeah.
we could be done.
You know...
...if that's what you want.
But that's not gonna
solve my problem.
So. listen. I'm gonna
let youse think about it.
Alright? You're gonna
come back. You'll see.
Now get the fuck out.
[tense music]
What the fuck was that?
No fuckin' idea.
But he needs us bad.
or we'd be fuckin' dead.
Where the fuck are we?
This is guinea country. Jimmy.
How the fuck would I know?
Hey. we ain't never selling
for that dago bastard. right?
Of course we're fuckin' not.
You crazy?
Sometimes. Jimmy.
[laugh]
You got money for a bus?
They'll be back.
[♪ Pullin Teeth ♪
by The Scratch playing]
♪ I was messing
at a gathering atop a hill ♪
♪ Of a brisk
and shepherd's morning ♪
♪ Air so cold you could
crack it on a knee ♪
♪ I train the eye
like an eagle ♪
♪ And watch the creatures
flee one by one ♪
♪ Sometimes you get lucky ♪
♪ Sometimes they'll disappear
back up their own arse ♪
♪ If it's not too mucky ♪
♪ If you're lucky ♪
♪ So smug and busy ♪
♪ Just another
suit yourself is he ♪
♪ He's an Irishman though ♪
♪ So smug and busy ♪
♪ Just another
suit yourself is he ♪
♪ He's an Irishman though ♪
♪ So stick your harps up
a yipaderry-o ♪
♪ So smug and busy ♪
♪ Just another
suit yourself is he ♪
♪ He's an Irishman though ♪
Subtitling: difuze